a little bit...
ちょっと...
lie?
嘘?
Why?
どうして?
no...
いや...
It's so cute.
めちゃくちゃ可愛いですね
No, not at all.
いや、全然
Idol...
アイドル...
Beautiful...
綺麗な...
Can I ask you a silly question?
ちょっとくだらない質問していいですか?
Is it your favorite food?
好きな食べ物なんですか?
Favorite food?
好きな食べ物?
It's omelet rice.
オムライスです
A little different...
ちょっと違う...
Really?
本当に?
I really like it.
本当に好きです
What kind of omelet rice do you like?
オムライスは何が好きですか?
taste.
味
taste?
味?
yes.
はい
Well, that's it.
まあ、それだけです
Why are you so cute?
なんでそんなに可愛いんですか?
Not at all.
全然ですよ
TRUE?
本当?
Yeah.
うん
It's really cute.
本当に可愛いですよ
Do you have a boyfriend?
彼氏いらっしゃいますか?
I don't have a boyfriend.
彼氏いないです
do not have?
ない?
Do you often get confessed to?
よく告白されたりするんですか?
No, not at all.
いや、 全然
I'm not involved.
関わらないです
With each person.
一人一人と
Not involved?
関わらない?
I'm not involved.
関わらないです
Not involved?
関 わらない?
yes.
はい
Why aren't you involved?
なんで関わらない?
It's like there's no chance.
機会がないというか
Not interested?
興味もない?
That's not the case though.
そういうわけじゃないですけど
Isn't that so?
そういうわけじゃない?
The nose is real.
鼻がリアル
It's always been that way.
ずっとそれですね
The nose is real.
鼻がリアル
My hands are warm.
手が温かいの
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Yeah.
うん
Well then, it's all too soon.
じゃあ、あっという間
When was the last time you had a pet?
最近ペッチしたっていつなんですか?
It was so long ago that I can't even remember.
結構前過ぎて思えてない
Was it quite a while ago?
結構前なの?
I agree.
そうですね
About a year ago?
1年くらい前?
Probably something like that.
多分そういうぐらい
Was it that long ago?
そんな前なの?
As who?
誰として?
With the senior I liked at that time.
その時好きだった先輩と
senior?
先輩?
Isn't that your boyfriend?
それ、彼氏じゃない?
boyfriend?
彼氏?
It's not my boyfriend.
彼氏ではないですね
Why do you do it?
なんでイチするの?
It kind of goes with the flow.
なんか、流れで
Seriously?
マジで?
Is it that person's house?
その人の家かな?
enviable.
羨ましい
You don't know, right?
知らないだろ?
i don't know.
知らない
What should I do?
どうしたらいい?
Are you going to fuck me?
えっちゃうの?
usually.
普通
usually?
普通?
Don't do it yourself.
自分でしたりしないで
I don't think so.
しないですね
Not at all?
全然しない?
Don't you feel horny?
ムラムラしたりしない?
Not much.
あんまり
Be smooth.
すべすべなれ
is that so?
そうですか?
It's because you're young.
若いからだね
Turn it yourself.
自分でめくって
Show me again.
もう一度見せて
Your skin is white.
肌白いね
I don't know.
わかんない
I think it's normal.
普通だと思います
Hey, boobs.
ちょっと、おっぱいさ
Can you turn it over a little more?
もうちょいめくれる?
What, do you have boobs?
何、おっぱいしてるの?
It's fresh, after all.
みずみずしいね、やっぱりね
fresh.
みずみずしい
It's so fresh.
みずしいよ
wonderful.
素晴らしい
I was nervous, amazing.
緊張したね、すごい
Because it's cute.
かわいいからね
For such a young child.
こんな、若い子に
Well, how old is he now?
あれ、今いくつなんだっけ?
I'm 20 years old now.
今、20歳です
Seriously?
まじで?
That's a dangerous guy.
やばい奴だよ、それ
That's dangerous, isn't it?
やばいですよね
How old are you?
何年生?
20th grade.
20年生
He's a dangerous guy, isn't he?
やばい奴だよね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I don't think it's okay.
大丈夫じゃないと思います
Well then, why don't you take off your top clothes?
じゃあさ、上の服脱げてよっか
Really, this.
ほんとに、これ
what?
何?
Last year, Edge meant it was amazing?
去年、エッジってことはすごいってこと?
Well, last year.
そうですね、去年
Wow, that's amazing.
うわ、すごい
soft.
柔らかい
I have some energy left, after all.
残力があるね、やっぱり
hey.
ね
Stand up for a moment, skirt too.
ちょっと 立ってさ、スカートもさ、
Is it okay?
いいんじゃうか?
It was really good.
ほんとに良かったよね
No, yeah.
いや、うん
Was it not stable?
安定してなかった?
It's beautiful, really.
綺麗だね、ほんとにね
No, not at all.
いや、全然
It's white.
白くて
hey.
ね
That's not the case, at all.
そんなことないですよ、全然
Do you have any club activities?
部活やってますか?
I haven't done it.
やってないです
Do, what, all the time?
やって、何、ずっと?
Just a little bit when I was in middle school.
中学の時に、ちょっとだけ
Did you do that?
やってたの?
For sports?
スポーツに?
yes.
はい
What were you doing?
何やってたの?
I was playing tennis.
テニスやってました
The back view is really beautiful.
めっちゃ後ろ姿が綺麗だね
Then look back and see where it came from.
じゃあ振り返ってみて、どっから
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
wonderful.
素晴らしい
Either is fine.
どっちでもいいですよ
It's really okay like that.
ほんとそういうの大丈夫なんで
You have it.
持ってるじゃん
Beauty.
美女
Get used to it.
なれ
it was good?
良かった?
no.
いや
Look at your own face.
自分の顔を見る
Try it with both hands in your panties.
両手パンツでしてみてさ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Does it match?
合ってます?
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
It doesn't fit at all.
全然入んない
I'm keeping it clean.
綺麗にしてるよ
I do it too.
僕もしてます
Oh, are you doing that?
あ、そうしてる?
what
何
Is there anything going on?
事 ある?
There is none.
無いです
tickles.
くすぐったい
Hey, look behind you, stand out,
ちょっとさ、後ろを見て、目立ついて、
Before that.
その前に
Oh, no, no.
あ、違う違う
Ah, this.
あ、この
Look behind you and stand out.
後ろを見て、目立つ
No, I really don't like it.
いや、本当に嫌だ
Isn't this long?
これ長くないですか?
Do you really hate it when you see something like a bonus?
本当におまけとか言うの見たら嫌なんですか?
long?
長い?
long.
長い
More crispy.
もっとサクッと
Wouldn't it be easier to fit it in and do it more quickly?
はめといて、もっとサクッとやるんじゃないですか?
I want to take a closer look.
じっくり見たいじゃん
No, really.
いや、本当に
I really don't like it.
本当に嫌だ
Seriously?
マジで?
Isn't it long?
長くないですか?
It's still good.
まだいいじゃん
No, no, I really don't like it.
いや いやいや、本当に嫌だ
Not yet?
まだですかね?
Can I finish?
終わりしていいですか?
behind.
後ろ
Wait a minute, just a little longer.
ちょっと待って、もうちょっとじゃん
I really don't like it.
本当に嫌だ
What?
何や?
It's really complex.
本当に、コンプレックスなんですよ
I like dark cuts though.
暗いカットいいんですけど
What's the complex?
何やコンプレックス?
I really don't like it.
本当に嫌だ
Well then, Wad-chan, take your clothes off.
じゃあ、ワッドちゃん脱いで
Is it already flying from behind?
後ろからはもう飛んでるんですか?
It's no good if it's flying from behind.
後ろから飛んでるってダメやん
It's flying from behind.
後 ろから飛んでる
It's smooth.
つるつるだね
Half-hearted.
中途半端
It's smooth.
つるつるだね
It feels like it was born.
生まれたままな感じだ
Are you raising your feet?
足上げてますか?
put your feet up
足上げて
Masu.
ます
It's really embarrassing.
本当 にさ、恥ずかしいんだね
Totally.
全 然
Open your pussy.
おまご開いてきて
What do you mean?
どういうことですか?
Like this.
こうやってとして
Like this, yes.
こうやって、そう
So, open it
で、開いてき
hand.
て
Just open it up, please.
ちょっと 開いてごらん、ちゃんと
beautiful.
きれい
not at all.
全然
I can see the difference between this person and this person.
違いが分かんですけど、この人とは
Good, dirty, dirty.
いいな、汚い、汚い
You can do it, right?
できるでしょ
This is it?
これる?
3 more kilometers.
もう3キロ
It's small.
狭いね
Is it narrow?
狭いですか?
It's small.
狭いね
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
My feet hurt.
足が痛い
Do your feet hurt?
足が痛い?
It's delicious.
うまいね
Yeah.
うん
a little bit.
ちょっと
Does it hurt a little?
ちょっと痛い?
copper?
どう?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
often?
よく?
No?
ダメ?
Does it hurt a little?
ちょっと痛い?
It hurts a little.
ちょっと痛いよ
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Yeah.
うん
See you then.
じゃあまた